I'm Mr. King Dice
我是骰子之王先生
I'm the gamest in the land
我是大陆上最皮的人
I never play nice
我从不认真玩耍
I'm the Devil's right hand man
我是恶魔的左臂右膀
I can't let you pass
我不能让你通过
Cause you ain't done everything
因为你还有事未完
Bring me those contracts
给我那些合同
Come on, bring them to the king
快点把他们给我
If you haven't finished your task
如果你不能完成你的任务
Haven't worked assiduously
如果你不能刻苦地完成你的任务
No I cannot let you pass
不 我就不会让步
Don't you mess with me
别惹我的麻烦
Don't mess with King Dice
别惹骰子之王的麻烦
Don't mess with me
别惹我的麻烦
Don't mess with him
别惹他的麻烦
Don't mess with King Dice
别惹骰子之王的麻烦
Don't mess with me
别惹我的麻烦
I'm Mr. King Dice
我是骰子之王先生
Heed just what I say
注意听我说的话
The Devil has his price
恶魔有他的代价
And I'll make sure you pay
而我会保证让你偿还
I don't have time to mess 'round
我没时间去折腾这些
And I hope you will agree
我希望你会同意
Bring me those contracts, pronto!
快点把合同给我
Don't you mess with me
别惹我的麻烦
Don't mess with King Dice
别惹骰子之王的麻烦
Don't mess with me
别惹我的麻烦
Don't mess with him
别惹他的麻烦
Don't mess with King Dice
别惹骰子之王的麻烦
Don't mess with me
别惹我的麻烦